Hello friends, welcome to your own
channel List of Education. In this channel,
you will get daily updates from the stock market.
Subscribe to this channel.
Friends, after subscribing to the channel,
do share the bell icon so that you
get daily updates. There could have been only one in the entire budget,
which was the biggest highlight, and from that, there are
many such big talks, keep writing.
Friends, I am talking about insurance
companies. If we talk about insurance companies, then there are
many such stocks which are listed and are
very good stocks. Also, if we
talk about news in it, that is, it was mentioned in the budget,
then we will see that
now half of it will be implemented,
which is 59% and perhaps you can check it,
but this time it has been increased to 40.
It is a good thing that foreign
investors have shown interest in it, and
if you invest money in that chapter, then
obviously this is the entire chapter of the sector's fortune.
This is the verse of the stock, so everyone will
benefit. So friends, if you look at the chart of
your listed stocks, then friends,
our first stock is HDFC
Life Insurance. If we
talk about it well, then you  It is 698 25
paise close with a rise of three percent,
so friends, talking about the tweet itself, it is
its right to Rs 731, it makes on January 11, 2021, we will keep
talking about Rs 300 40 per kg,
which was made on March 23, 2019, if we
can talk about delivery on this, 44.35
percent delivery has been taken, if we
talk about quantity, then more than 37 lakh 18 thousand
quantity has been taken
on delivery basis, so friends, if we talk about this hair,
you will see that as soon as it
made its high, after that correction
started in it and after the correction, this price had gone
down a lot, so friends, there was a very
good buying opportunity that at that
time when it was making its own, now see, the
award had also happened, so correction was also necessary
and after the correction, the job also bombed in it,
that is a very good thing, friends, now if we
talk about big English, then next let us
talk about how effective it can be for it,
if it is showing on the ticket in the data
Talking about changes, you will see that next
year the target for cashew is
showing a growth of around 25%.
If we talk about it, it is Rs 830. It has been
decided that next year its
low expectation target will be up to Rs 830, which
means that friends,
growth of more than 22% will be seen.
Next year, one can invest in this stock,
but if we
talk about its peers, there are
rebel stocks of the sector where you will see a growth of up to 40%. If you do
not believe the drop, then I will show you its data as well.
Our next stock today
is SBI Life Insurance. If we talk about it too, then
using 877, this close bar shows a
rise of about one and a half percent.
We will see further growth of Rs 1017. Its first
fruit was made on 30th January 2020,
after which it was shared but
again it could not grow there, so now a
very good MP has
tweeted two photos of protest, people are praying, then up to 500 19040
paise  It had fallen down, you will see that
after the delivery in the entry on 19 March 2019, definitely see that the
quantity of slug 42 thousand has been
picked up from the delivery bay, so if we talk about Guys Har, then
this Robert happened, after that the
collection came and after that
it is trying to handle it by just searching and moving, so let's see
what opinion do they give on the big list, how much growth are they
showing regarding this layer, so if
SBI Life is talked about, you will see that the
big Ellis is saying that
this share will see a cut of up to Rs 1209,
that the level of Bigg Boss was also crossed yesterday, after
crossing the level of thousand, it is going to go much
above that and talking about the growth in Guys,
Bedi is estimating a growth of about 40 percent
next year, so
friends and if foreign
investors from you come and invest some money
in these sectors, then this chapter is going to go even
higher, so friends,
money can be invested in these sectors, okay, you must have
seen that before the Twenty20, that is,
in the elections, on the 19th  If seen,
most of the money was made from here and in the
coming time this page setup will be considered very self
and soon this chapter grows very fast,
then money can be invested in this city, next let's
talk about a [ __ ] rule,
Prudential Life Insurance, that is, these
three companies of ours belong to real life
insurance,
talking about career, 827 rupees 50 paise expert is running,
if we talk about the boom, then it was
showing a boom of 1.35 percent in today's date,
friends, now let's talk about it, it was spread at
64531 at 90.65 because on 11th March 2021
it had made its new work, after that there was a
correction in it too, now we will see that the
tweet people 22610 paise which was made on 24th March, if we
talk about delivery, then 42%
delivery has been taken, quantity of 27 lakh shares has been taken, so
friends, if we talk about this city, then as soon as it happens a
lot, then it is
necessary to have a correction in the share
and if the share  If they are corrected, then
after that, when it is there, then it shows a very healthy growth
and after that it goes up to a great height, after
seeing that, their title has been
suggested, big list friends,
if we talk about this hair, then you will see that the
number that has changed in it is
Rs 695, that is, up to about ₹100, if we
talk about growth, then a
growth of more than four points has been shown, a growth of 44.25 percent, it is being
told that in the next one year,
that is, in next January 2021,
you will get to see a target of about Rs 700 cut in it
and at this time, you have got much
below it, so obviously friends,
if you have seen a growth of 4045 portion, then
these sales can be considered
for the long term, friends, this is the
sector which is a very chapter, so it can be
invested in the house, the
extra one is ICICI Lombard
General Insurance, if we are talking like this, at that
time it went up by 1376 in 10 back and if we talk about today's
growth, then you  You will see that it was
showing a growth of 4.61 percent as of today,
this share was the most invested,
well now we will talk about Idu cutting 1626
at 45 paise, who made it on 6th January
2021, if we talk about these facts, then
it was made at ₹800 on 19th March afternoon, if we can talk about delivery, the
delivery of 46.9 lakhs has been taken up on 8th, well, the
quantity of more than 90 lakhs, so let's
see that, if we look at it and
share it after the board is there, it was also going to be difficult
because after that when Bhavana Star will do
this share, I think it will go 2000 plus, we can
see very easily, what do they say, then
this hair is wrong, you will
see that the number around 1900 has been suggested in it, that means this
share can go up to 1900, at that time, like this
Urmila 1385, that is, you can see the growth
that this much is a lot and if we
talk about its quantity without percentage, then
44% in this also  That growth can be seen,
which I am telling in big English,
so go and tell friends
and if more apps are included then
Jaiswal, this is not just going to go
up by four but much more than that, so friends,
inches can be considered, so
that's all for today, like,
share and subscribe to the video, thank
you for watching this video.